BYIRINGIRO Aime Fils

I passionate in a software Development especially in MERN Stack Development especially I used to work in groups and sharing with other. Rwanda-Kigali (+250) 790154696 / 738107117 aimefils173@gmail.com

INTRODUCTION.

I am the Rwandan, I live in Rubavu District and Rugerero sector ,I'm 19 years old and gender is Male I am also last born in my family.My parents are NDAYAMBAJE Iledephonse(Father) and NYIRANGIRIMANA Annociatha.and also I am christian in New life Bible Church Rubavu.

EXPERIENCE

Africa New Ministries Rubavu, Volunteer

From 2022-2024- PRESENT.

I'm volunteering at ANLM Rubavu in children sponsorship.I am also a church member at New Life Bible Church-Rubavu.

Eshuri Data Ltd, Intern

15 May 2024- 03 April 2024.

I have completed an internship at Eshuri Ltd by sharpening my skill and knowledge in Software Development Trade.

EDUCATION

Ecole Secondaire Technique Gisenyi, Report Card.

September 2022 - PRESENT

I'm a student at ESTG in the Information Communication and Technology sector and Trade Software Development in Level Five(L5). Apart from Class I used to attend I Debate course and Debate Club.

Groupe Scolaire Umubano I, Gisenyi — Result slip

JANUARY 2018 - July 2022.

I completed three years at Gs Umubano I in Ordinary Level.and I was a member of Group Bublic Secondaire. I have a result slip from Nesa.

SKILLS

Digital Skills Certificate. (Computer Skill.)

Microsoft Office(Ms Word, Ms Excel and Ms representation).

Time management.

Letter translations and Filling System.

AWARDS

I have Completed course with Digital skills.

I participated in Wavumbuzi
Entrepreneur Challenge Edition 4(2024)

LANGUAGES

Writing Speaking

1.English Very Good Very Good2.kinyarwanda Excellent Excellent

MY HOBBIES.

- 1. Sing and Sound Controlling.
- 2. Coding and Listing Music.

$\textbf{Groupe Scolaire Stella Maris} \ , \ \textbf{Gisenyi} - \textit{National result}$

JANUARY 2012 - DECEMBER 2018.

I completed six years at Glsenyi Stella Maris In Primary School.

I have a primary certificate from Rwanda Education Board.